e
[Music]
I started this channel in the spring
having moved to a little cottage and not
sure what I was going to do with my life
and so it seems fitting that I am here
now years later facing something new
once again this month has been rather
emotional but important nonetheless as
I've realized that the time has come to
say goodbye
[Music]
my son will be born very soon and I
promised myself as well as people in my
life I deeply love that I will take some
time to get suited into this new era
making no definite plans and instead
seeing what happens as no doubt I will
need a little time to know where my soul
is leading
[Music]
me I naturally nervous about becoming a
parent but I found myself succeeding far
better in life by sitting down and
looking at my fears once in a while
taking them out into the Sun and sharing
them with the wild
flowers if you didn't know flowers are
very wise that may be because fairies
are their best friends they always
remind me that they bloom despite the
possibility of drought and fire because
if they don't they'll stay a seed or
slowly shrivel into a dry root ball then
they would never get the chance to see
how beautiful they could truly be I'm
keeping this in mind as I prepare to
take time to settle into a new life how
beautiful can each of us be if we let go
I don't know the answer for myself but I
certainly am going to find out a bit
more today and tomorrow and the day
after and so on until the very
end you've seen me evolve so much from
the beginning of this channel as I went
on the hard but rewarding journey of
learning how to thrive as a rather
sensitive soul that meant embracing more
balance more being deeply questioning my
drive to do more and be more and instead
wondering what is doing enough and being
enough the answer I found was to just
begin to step into the unknown to give
it a try
[Music]
I have put my heart and soul into my
videos for years and I hope you will
continue to enjoy them knowing my love
is imbued in each and everyone I hope to
see you again once I'm settled in with
my son and we'll share good news as it
comes however I'm trying not to make
plans so what I will say is goodbye for
now keep shining your light always and
know that you are loved
[Music]
it feels like the house is in a bit of
uproar right now because baby could be
here pretty much any day and there are
so many little things to do and get done
that it felt like we were in a good
place but things keep popping up so
we're working on all of that getting
quite busy and I'm going to see how
things go I'm hoping it will all go well
I wanted to give you just a few
announcements and that is that I do have
pre-orders for the hardback version of
my book The Cottage fairy companion
available if you are interested there is
never any obligation but I I just wanted
to give a little announcement it was
rather exciting I'm going to be signing
them all there's going to be book plates
in each one that are signed and I'm
going to be including some of my own
printed bookmarks in some of them but I
still am working on all that so there
will be uh pre-orders available if you
are interested there's also the
paperback version as well of course but
I also have a database of meditation
sessions that I've recorded with
soundscapes as well as short sto stories
that I've recorded and some videos on
patreon if you're interested in that as
well and want to support the channel
during this impending little Hiatus and
we're going to see where life takes us
from there I always like to give those
options in case someone is interested
but your love and well wishes is more
than enough and I just appreciate you
being here and I'm sending you so much
love goodbye